A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1953-2004
Library of Virginia
- II. Commissioner's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1995-2003., Extent: 37 cubic feet (37 boxes). (Box 61-97)
  - 1998
    - Federal Milk Marketing Order (Box 74)
    - Federal State Meat Inspection Program (Box 74)
    - Fee Schedules - VDACS (Box 74)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 74)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 74)
    - General Assembly (Box 74)
    - 1998 General Assembly Bills (Box 74)
    - 1998 General Assembly Guidelines (Box 74)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Governor's Office (Box 74)
    - Harrisonburg Lab (Box 74)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Grain Grading Program (Box 74)
    - Hog Farm (Box 74)
    - Horse Council, Virginia (Box 74)
    - House of Representatives (US) (Box 74)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Hydrilla Cooperative Project (Box 74)
    - Information Management, Council on (Box 74)
    - Virginia Information Providers Network (VIPNET) (Box 74)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Information Technology Advisory Group (Box 74)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 74)
    - James City County Growers Cooperative (Box 74)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Labor, Dept. of (US) (Box 74)
    - Law and Office Automation (VDACS) (Box 74)
    - Land Use (Box 74)
    - 1998 Legislative Proposals (Box 74)
    - Legislation (Box 74)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Liaison Office, Virginia (Box 75)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 75)
    - Mandates, Federal (Box 75)
    - Milk Commission, Virginia (Box 75)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Minnesota Milk Producers Case (Box 75)
    - National Governors' Association (Box 75)
    - Northern Neck Virginia Farmers Market (Box 75)
    - Open for Agribusiness, Virginia is (Box 75)
    - Performance Measures (Box 75)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Pfiesteria (Box 75)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Poultry Litter Issues (Box 75)
    - Poultry Litter Study (Box 75)
    - VDACS 98-99 Process Review Teams (Box 75)
    - Ratites Study Report (Box 75)
    - Richmond Livestock Export Facility (Box 75)
    - Rural Rehabilitation Trust Fund (Box 75)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 75)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 75)
    - Senators (Box 75)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 75)
    - Sole Source (Box 75)
    - Southern States (Box 75)
    - State Fair (Box 75)
    - Strategic Planning (Box 75)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 75)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Treasury, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS (Box 75)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - AG in the Classroom (Box 75)
    - AG 2000 Transition Task Force (Box 75)
    - AG Week 1998 (Box 75)
    - Agenda - SMT (Box 75)
    - AG News Releases (Box 75)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Apple Board, Virginia (Box 75)
    - Apples - Mexico (Box 75)
    - Aquaculture (Box 75)
    - Aquaculture Study Report (Box 75)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 75)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 75)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 75)
    - Awards Committee, VDACS (Box 75)
    - Poultry and Egg (Box 75)
    - Boll Weevil (Box 75)
    - Capital Budget Proposals, 1998-2000 (Box 75)
    - Century Farm Program (Box 75)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 75)
    - Charlottesville Farmers Market (Box 75)
    - Code Commission, Virginia (Box 75)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 75)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 75)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 76)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 76)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 76)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 76)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 76)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (CAAC) (Box 76)
    - Crop Insurance (Box 76)
    - Dairymen's Association of Virginia (Box 76)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 76)
    - Delegates (Box 76)
    - Disasters (2) (Box 76)
    - Disasters (1) (Box 76)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 76)
    - Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Growers Advisory Committee (Box 76)
    - Economic Development (Box 76)
    - Economic Impact Brochure (Box 76)
    - Education, Department of (Box 76)
    - EEO Committee (Box 76)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 76)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of (Box 76)
    - VDACS Employees Governor's Survey (Box 76)
  - 1999
    - Aquaculture (Box 77)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 77)
    - Audits - Internal (Box 77)
    - Audit - Office of Laboratory Services (Box 77)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 77)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 77)
    - Awards Committee, VDACS (Box 77)
    - Budget Amendments, 1998-2000 (Box 77)
    - Virginia Cattle Industry Board (Box 77)
    - Century Farm Program (Box 77)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 77)
    - Virginia Charity Food Advisory Board (Box 77)
    - Charlottesville Farmers' Market (Box 77)
    - Code Commission, Virginia (Box 77)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 77)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 77)
    - Commodity Boards (Box 77)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 77)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 77)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 77)
    - Congressional Issues (Box 77)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 77)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (CAAC) (Box 77)
    - Cotton Gin (Box 77)
    - Cotton Industry Study Group (Box 77)
    - Crab - Blue (Box 77)
    - Dairy Compact, Southern (3) (Box 77)
    - Dairy Compact, Southern (2) (Box 77)
    - Dairy Compact, Southern (1) (Box 77)
    - Dairymen's Association, Virginia (Box 77)
    - Delegates (Box 77)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 77)
    - Disasters (1) (Box 77)
    - Disasters (2) (Box 77)
    - Disasters (3) (Box 78)
    - State Disaster Recovery Task Force (Box 78)
    - East Blue Ridge Farmers' Shipping Point Market (Box 78)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 78)
    - Elk (Box 78)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 78)
    - Regional Employee Meetings (Box 78)
    - Employee Relations Council, Dept. of (Box 78)
    - EPA (Box 78)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 78)
    - Administrative and Financial Services (Box 78)
    - Halbleib, Craig M. (Box 78)
    - Allegeier, Jerry P. (Box 78)
    - Information Systems (Box 78)
    - Garey, Louis M. (Box 78)
    - Facilities Management (Box 78)
    - Martin, Teddy R. (Box 78)
    - Procurement (Box 78)
    - Finance Office (Box 78)
    - Sims, William D. (Box 78)
    - Animal Industry Services (Box 78)
    - Butts, Donald W. (Box 78)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 78)
    - Alverez, Andy - Office of Consumer Affairs (Box 78)
    - Office of Consumer Services Report of Activities, 1999 (Box 78)
    - Office of Dairy and Foods (Box 78)
    - Endangered Species (Box 78)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS (Box 79)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 79)
    - AG 2000 Transition Task Force (Box 79)
    - Agenda - SMT (Box 79)
    - AG Economic Impact (Box 79)
    - Apple Board, Virginia (Box 79)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 79)
    - Sole Source (Box 79)
    - Southern States (Box 79)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Cooperative, Inc., Investigative Report (Box 79)
    - State Fair (Box 79)
    - State Police (Box 79)
    - 1998-2000 Biennial Strategic Plan (Box 79)
    - Strategic Planning Initiatives (Box 79)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 79)
    - Tobacco (1) (Box 79)
    - Tobacco (2) (Box 79)
    - Tobacco (3) (Box 79)
    - Virginia Tobacco Trust Certification Board (Box 79)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization (Box 79)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 79)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 79)
    - Travel Process Review Team (Box 79)
    - USDA (2) (Box 79)
    - USDA (1) (Box 80)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 80)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (Box 80)
    - VPI and SU (Box 80)
    - Virginia Strategy (1) (Box 80)
    - Virginia Strategy (2) (Box 80)
    - Year 2000 Status Reports (Box 80)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 80)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council (Box 80)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 80)
    - Virginia Charity Food Assistance Advisory Board (Box 80)
    - Virginia Farmers Market System (Box 80)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 80)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 80)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 80)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 80)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 80)
    - SASDA (Box 80)
    - SUSTA (Box 80)
    - NASDA (1) (Box 80)
    - Suggested Response (1) (Box 80)
    - Environmental Quality (Box 81)
    - EEO Committee (Box 81)
    - Farm Bureau Federation (Box 81)
    - Farmers Market - Retail (Box 81)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 81)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Dept. (Box 81)
    - Governor's Office (Box 81)
    - Governor's Technology Award (Box 81)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Horse Council of Virginia (Box 81)
    - House of Representatives (US) (Box 81)
    - House and Community Development, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Information Management, Council on (Box 81)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 81)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) (Box 81)
    - 1999 Legislative Proposals (Box 81)
    - Legislation (1) (Box 81)
    - Legislation (2) (Box 81)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Liaison Office, Virginia (Box 81)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 81)
    - Mandates, Federal (Box 81)
    - Maryland and Virginia Milk Producers Cooperative Association (Box 81)
    - Metrology Laboratory (Box 81)
    - Milk Commission, Virginia (Box 81)
    - Model General Assembly - YMCA (Box 81)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of (Box 81)
    - Performance Measures (Box 81)
    - Piedmont/Roanoke Growers' Cooperative (Box 81)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 81)
    - Plasticulture (Box 81)
    - Poultry Litter Issues (Box 81)
    - Process Review Team (Box 81)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 82)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 82)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 82)
    - Senators (Box 82)
    - Smyth Food Service (Box 82)
  - 2000
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Co-Op (Box 83)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board Meeting, 25 February 1999 (Box 83)
    - State Police, Dept. of (Box 83)
    - 1998-2000 Strategic Plan (Box 83)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000-2002 (Box 83)
    - Subscriptions - Agency (Box 83)
    - Task Force - Emergency Services (Box 83)
    - Task Force on Food Safety (Box 83)
    - Task Force on Pfiesteria (Box 83)
    - Task Force on Virginia Seafood Marketing (Box 83)
    - Taxation, Dept. of - Proposal - Tax Elimination (Box 83)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 83)
    - Technology, Secretary of (Box 83)
    - Tobacco (Box 83)
    - VDACS Tobacco Region Task Force (Box 83)
    - Memorandum of Understanding between VDACS and Tob. Indem. And Comm. Revit. Comm. (Box 83)
    - Virginia Tobacco Settlement Foundation (Box 83)
    - Minutes, Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (Box 83)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (2) (Box 83)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (1) (Box 83)
    - Virginia Tobacco Trust Certification Board (Box 84)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 84)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 84)
    - Travel, Blanket (Box 84)
    - USDA (3) (Box 84)
    - USDA (2) (Box 84)
    - USDA (1) (Box 84)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (Box 84)
    - Virginia Naturally 2000 (Box 84)
    - VPI and SU (Box 84)
    - Office of Dairy and Foods (Box 84)
    - Endangered Species (Box 84)
    - Pesticides (Box 84)
    - Lawson, Marvin - Office of Pesticide Services (Box 84)
    - Rogers, Alan - Product and Industry Standards (Box 84)
    - Eggborn, Phil - Plant and Pest Services (Box 84)
    - Sleight, Thomas (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing (Box 84)
    - Commodity Services (Box 85)
    - Grain Grading (Box 85)
    - Office of International Marketing (Box 85)
    - Fruit and Vegetable Fees (Box 85)
    - Peanut Inspection Fee Schedule (Box 85)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 85)
    - AG in the Classroom (Box 85)
    - AG 2000 Transition Task Force (Box 85)
    - Agenda, SMT (Box 85)
    - AG Economic Impact (Box 85)
    - Virginia Agricultural Vitality Program (Box 85)
    - American Farmland Trust (Box 85)
    - Anguilla Culture Technology, Inc. (Box 85)
    - Virginia Apple Board (Box 85)
    - Apple Juice Anti-Dumping Case (Box 85)
    - Aquaculture (Box 85)
    - Atlantic Rural Expo (Box 85)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 85)
    - Audits, Internal (Box 85)
    - Audit - Office of Laboratory Services (Box 85)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 85)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 85)
    - VDACS Awards Committee (Box 85)
    - Employee Bonus Payments (Box 85)
    - Budget Amendments 2000-2002 (Box 85)
    - Virginia Cattle Industry Board (Box 85)
    - Century Farm Program (Box 85)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 85)
    - Virginia Charity Food Advisory Board (Box 85)
    - Charlottesville Farmers Market (Box 85)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation (Box 85)
    - Virginia Code Commission (Box 85)
    - Coles, John (Setoff Debt Collection) (Box 85)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 85)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 85)
    - Commodity Boards (Box 85)
    - Commodity Grading Advisory Committee (Box 85)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 85)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 85)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 85)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 85)
    - Congressional Issues (Box 85)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 85)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 85)
    - Cotton Gin (Box 85)
    - Cotton Industry Study Group (Box 85)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 85)
    - Crab - Blue (Box 85)
    - Dairy Compact (Box 85)
    - Virginia Dairymen's Association (Box 85)
    - Defense Department - Produce Procurement (Box 85)
    - Delegates (Box 85)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 85)
    - Disasters (Box 85)
    - Disaster Assistance to Virginia's Farmers, Report, 11/2000 (Box 85)
    - Disaster Assistance Study Group (Box 85)
    - Dogfish Fishery (Box 85)
    - East Blue Ridge Farmers' Shipping Point Market (Box 85)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 85)
    - Education, Dept. ofEmergency Services, Dept. of (Box 85)
    - VDACS Emergency Response Manual (Box 85)
    - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. (Box 85)
    - Employee Recognition Program (Box 85)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (US) (Box 85)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 85)
    - EPA Proposed Regulation - Confined Animal Feeding Operations (Box 86)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (US) (Box 86)
    - EEO Committee (Box 86)
    - 2000 Farm Bill (Box 86)
    - Virginia Farmers Market System (Box 86)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 86)
    - Fees - Inspection - Fruit and Vegetables (Box 86)
    - First Aid (Box 86)
    - Food and Drug Administration (2) (Box 86)
    - Food and Drug Administration (1) (Box 86)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 86)
    - Fruit Market Feasibility Study (Box 86)
    - FTE Reduction (Box 86)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Governor's Office (Box 86)
    - Grants (Box 86)
    - Grievance Procedures (Box 86)
    - Thomas E. Tatum - Grievance (Box 86)
    - Harrisonburg Laboratory (Box 86)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Virginia Horse Council (Box 86)
    - House of Representatives (US) (Box 86)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. (Box 86)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 86)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 86)
    - Land Preservation Briefing (Box 86)
    - Land Use (Box 86)
    - Legislative Proposals, 2000 (Box 86)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Virginia Liaison Office (Box 86)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 86)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and Tobacco Indem. Com. Revit. Com. (Box 86)
    - Federal Mandates (Box 86)
    - Metrology Lab (Box 86)
    - Migrant Worker (Box 86)
    - Virginia Milk Commission (Box 86)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - National Farm Animal Identification and Records (Box 86)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of (Box 86)
    - Perdue (Box 86)
    - Piedmont-Roanoke Facility (Box 86)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Plasticulture (1) (Box 86)
    - Plasticulture (2) (Box 86)
    - Productivity Savings Plan (Box 86)
    - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Dept. of (Box 86)
    - Agency Publications (Box 86)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 86)
    - Recodification of Title 3.1 of Code of Virginia (Box 86)
    - Rocco, Inc. (Box 86)
    - Rotational Survey Proposal (Box 86)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission (Box 86)
    - Salary Administration Plan (Box 86)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 86)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 86)
    - Senators (Box 87)
    - Report to Senate Finance Committee (Box 87)
    - Senate Finance Tour, 9/2000 (Box 87)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 87)
    - Sole Source (Box 87)
    - Goats Milk (Box 87)
    - Southern States (Box 87)
    - Southeast Farmers Market (1) (Box 87)
    - Southeast Farmers Market (2) (Box 87)
    - Voice Mail (Box 87)
    - Virginia College Savings Plan (Box 87)
    - Virginia Strategy (Box 87)
    - Water Plan (Box 87)
    - Water Results in Washington Building Floors (Box 87)
    - Wetlands (Box 87)
    - Year 2000 (Box 87)
    - YMCA (Box 87)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 87)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council (Box 87)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 87)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 87)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 87)
    - Virginia Pest Control Board (Box 87)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 87)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 87)
    - NASDA (Box 87)
    - SASDA (Box 87)
    - SUSTA (Box 87)
  - 2001
    - Audit - Office of Laboratory Services (AIS) (Box 88)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 88)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS (Box 88)
    - Budget Amendments, 2000-2002 (Box 88)
    - Brucellosis (Box 88)
    - Cattle Industry Board (Box 88)
    - Charity Food Advisory Board (Box 88)
    - Charlottesville Farmers Market (Box 88)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation (Box 88)
    - Virginia Code Commission (Box 88)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 88)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 88)
    - Commodity Boards (Box 88)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 88)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 88)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 88)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 88)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 88)
    - Cotton Gin (Box 88)
    - Cotton Industry Group (Box 88)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 88)
    - Crab - Blue (Box 88)
    - USDA Specialty Crop and Ag. Promotion Grants (Box 88)
    - Dairy Compact (Box 88)
    - Virginia Dairymen's Association (Box 88)
    - Defense Department - Produce Procurement (Box 88)
    - Delegates (Box 88)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 88)
    - Disasters (Box 88)
    - Disaster Assistance to Virginia's Farmers Report 11/01 (Box 88)
    - Disaster Assistance Study Group (Box 88)
    - Disaster Recovery Task Force (Box 88)
    - Dogfish Fishery (Box 88)
    - East Blue Ridge Farmers Shipping Point Market (Box 88)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 88)
    - Economic and Disaster Assistance Study, SJ 162 and SJ 236 (Box 88)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 88)
    - Executive Order 65 (Box 88)
    - Electronic Document Management (Box 88)
    - VDACS Emergency Response Manual (Box 88)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 88)
    - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of (empty) (Box 88)
    - Employee Recognition Program (empty) (Box 88)
    - Endangered Species Regulation (Box 88)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 88)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 88)
    - EEO Committee (Box 88)
    - Executive Order 51 (Box 88)
    - Farm Bill (Box 88)
    - Farmers Market System Report, 2000 (Box 88)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 88)
    - Farmers Market Bill (Box 88)
    - Virginia Farmers Market System (Box 88)
    - Food and Drug Administration (1) (Box 88)
    - Food and Drug Administration (2) (Box 89)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 89)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Governor's Office (Box 89)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Virginia Horse Center - Economic Impact (Box 89)
    - Virginia Horse Council (Box 89)
    - House Bill 957 (Box 89)
    - House of Representatives (US Congress) (Box 89)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Information Technology Strategic Plan for VDACS 2002-2004 (Box 89)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Interior, U.S. Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Virginia Invasive Species Workgroup (Box 89)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 2001 Interim Financial Report (Box 89)
    - Laboratory/Office Complex, VDACS-Shenandoah (Box 89)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Land Use (Box 89)
    - 2001 Legislative Guidelines (Box 89)
    - Legislative Proposals, 2001 (Box 89)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - 2001 Legislative Studies and Reports (Box 89)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 89)
    - Federal Mandates (Box 89)
    - MOU - VDACS and Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (Box 89)
    - Metrology Labs (Box 89)
    - 2 VAC 5-531 Regulations Governing Milk for Manufacturing Purposes (Box 89)
    - Virginia Milk Commission (Box 89)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of (Box 89)
    - Organic Certification (Box 89)
    - Organic Certification Study Report (Box 89)
    - USDA National Organic Program (Box 89)
    - Perdue (Box 89)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 89)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 89)
    - Ratmink (Box 89)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 89)
    - Seat Management (Box 89)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry (Box 89)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 89)
    - Senate Finance Subcommittee (Box 89)
    - Senators (Box 89)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 89)
    - Sole Source (Box 89)
    - Solem, Christine (Box 89)
    - Southern States (Box 90)
    - Southeast Farmers Market (Box 90)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Cooperative (Box 90)
    - State Police, Dept. of (Box 90)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000-2002 (Box 90)
    - Strategic Planning Initiatives (Box 90)
    - Subscriptions, Agency (Box 90)
    - Task Force - Emergency Services (Box 90)
    - Task Force - Food Safety (Box 90)
    - Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel (Box 90)
    - Virginia Post Attack Economic Response Task Force (Box 90)
    - Virginia Post Attack Economic Response Task Force Meeting, 10 October 2001 (Box 90)
    - Virginia Post Attack Economic Task Force (Box 90)
    - Task Force on Seafood Marketing (Box 90)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 90)
    - Technology, Secretary of (Box 90)
    - Tobacco (Box 90)
    - Tobacco Trust Certification Board (Box 90)